Muhammad Amin Bin Zainal No. 40, Jalan Indah 1/19, Taman Universiti Indah, 43300, Seri Kembangan, Selangor Darul Ehsan.

Tel: +6012-6257751 Email: aminzainalk@gmail.com

Human Resources Manager,

Dear Sir,

## **APPLICATION FOR ENGINEER**

I am writing to express my interest for the position of engineer especially on mechanical in your company. I want to become an engineer because I have interest in designing and moving parts that make me want to know how it works and their principles. I have desire to learn from the team and willingness to experience new opportunity.

As a Mechanical Engineering student, I am equipped with the necessary knowledge that comes with the position including product development, technical drawings, and mechanical systems. Furthermore, my favourite subjects are manufacturing process and automation.

My working experience includes:

- Clerical and supervising skill I got a task to handle project at Celcom Axiata Berhad. From that, I be able to make a report using Microsoft Excel. I also use AutoCad to make layout plan for new project. Monitor vendor is one of my job scope that want to update progress work and make sure everything done within timeline.
- Interpersonal skill I attended the SL1M Booster Training at Sime Darby Berhad. I use this skill to cooperate with others to complete the project and the outcome was successful. Project was completed within a week.
- Analytical skill During internship with DH Robotics and Automation, to complete the task given, which is to make a robot's body. I use all the facts that I know before start drawing. The product was efficient and only one step for troubleshoot.

For additional details regarding my qualification and expertise, please review my attached resume.

Thank you	for taking	the time to	consider thi	s application	and I look t	forward to	hearing from
you.							

Sincerely,			
(MUHAMM	AD AMI	N ZAIN	IAI.)



# MUHAMMAD AMIN BIN ZAINAL

Bachelor of Engineering (Mechanical)

Seeking a full time position in a company that offers challenging job opportunity in mechanical engineering that will utilize strong technical and analytical skills.

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Address: No. 40, Jalan 1/19, Taman Universiti Indah, 43300, Seri Kembangan, Selangor

Age : 26 years

**Contact** : 019-3847751(Mobile) 03-89594887 (Home)

**Email** : aminzainalk@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION**

2012 – 2017 Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) Bachelor of Engineering (Mechanical)

**CGPA:** 2.95/4.00 **Project:** Design of an Intake Manifold

**2009 – 2012** Politeknik Seberang Perai (PSP) **Diploma of Engineering (Mechanical)** 

**CGPA:** 3.20/4.00 **Project:** Automated Banana Crisps

**2007 – 2008** Sek. Men. Teknik Sepang **Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia** 

**SPM:** 1A, 4B, 3C **Project:** Cup Holder

## **LANGUAGES**

- Malay

thinking

**SKILLS** 

InterpersonalCoaching

/Mentoring - Supervising

- Leadership

- Care-giving

- Analytical/logical

- Critical thinking

- English

#### **SOFTWARE**

- Microsoft Office
- AutoCAD
- SolidWorks3D

# REFERENCES JEEVAN GABRIEL

Head of Building Maintenance and Services

jeevanga@celcom.co m.my

019-3100900

## **ASMI ASHAARI**

Electrical Engineer,
DH Robotic &
Automation
admin@dhrobotic.co
m

013-3099160

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

6/2017 - Present Celcom Axiata Berhad. SL1M Trainee(Project Coordinator)

- Designed layout plan using AutoCAD (Menara Celcom, Menara Atlan, Menara 238)
- Purchased the work related for nationwide (RFT, RFQ, BoQ)
- Coordinated project (Open Space, Relocation staff and IT vendor).

5/2017 - 5/2017 Sime Darby Plantation Sdn. Bhd. SL1M Booster Training

- Implemented all the modules that provided by Sime Darby.
- Assembled a project that called Rakaat Plus for Innovation Fair.
- Teamed with other SL1M participants to run the Innovation Fair going smoothly.

6/2015 – 9/2015 DH Robotic & Automation Technical Support (Trainee)

- Designed robot body by focus on wheel turning radius and material.
- Purchased robot component with proper documentation to get sponsorship.
- Serviced the automation system like water gate and closed circuit camera.

11/2010 – 4/2011 Chee Leat Engineering Sdn. Bhd Assistant Supervisor (Trainee)

- Generated coding for CNC machine by using CAM software.
- Modified coding and tooling for CNC machine.
- Assisted and measured products for quality control.

2009 – 2017 McDonalds (Crew Leader), KFC, Secret Recipe Restaurant Crew

 Customer oriented – Served customer with good condition although in fast environment

## **ACTIVITIES**

2016	Stop the Crash ASEAN 2016		2016	Conference of Occupational Safety
				and Health (OSH) 2016